this video is about strategies best
这部影片是关于最佳策略的
response and Nash equilibrium in the
反应和纳什均衡
perfect information extensive form let's
完善的信息广泛形式让我们
look again at the sharing game and what
再看一下分享游戏以及什么
you see here and now instead of just
您现在就在这里看到而不仅仅是
thinking about what this game models I
考虑这个游戏的模型我
want to think about it in terms of
想从以下方面考虑
strategies so in a normal form game it
策略，所以在正常形式的游戏中
was easy to talk about pure strategies
谈论纯策略很容易
pure strategies were just actions but
纯粹的策略只是行动，但
you can see in an extensive form game
您可以在广泛的形式游戏中看到
there are sort of multiple places where
有很多地方
players get to choose different actions
玩家可以选择不同的动作
and so strategies are going to need to
所以策略就需要
be something a little bit more
多一点
complicated so I want to ask you to
很复杂，所以我想请你
think about how many pure strategies
想想有多少个纯策略
each player has in this game you may
每个玩家在这个游戏中都有
like to pause the video at this point
想在此时暂停视频
and work this out for yourself before I
在我之前自己解决这个问题
tell you the answer we'll start by
告诉你答案，我们将从
thinking about player 1 player 1 is kind
考虑玩家1玩家1是友善的
of easy because there's only one choice
之所以容易，是因为只有一种选择
node 4 player 1 here and so player 1 has
节点4的玩家1在这里，因此玩家1拥有
the three pure strategies that you would
您将要采用的三种纯策略
expect taking this action this action
期望采取这个行动这个行动
and this section things are a little bit
这个部分的事情有点
more complicated for player 2 because
对玩家2而言更为复杂，因为
player 2 has three choice nodes so the
玩家2具有三个选择节点，因此
number of pure strategies for player 1
玩家1的纯策略数量
is actually 8 rather than 6 player 1 has
实际上是8位玩家，而不是6位玩家1
six different actions but the reason
六种不同的动作，但原因
that there are eight pure strategies is
有八种纯策略是
that a pure strategy really is every
一个纯粹的策略真的是每一个
combination of choices that player two
玩家二的选择组合
could make kind of in the aggregate so
可以总的来说是这样
if player 2 oops if player two were to
如果玩家2失败，如果玩家2失败
choose like this it's a player 2 is to
选择像这样的玩家2
make the decision that in this situation
做出在这种情况下的决定
he would decline the offer in this
他会拒绝这个提议
situation he would accept it and then
他会接受的情况，然后
again in this situation he would decline
再次在这种情况下，他会拒绝
it that's one pure strategy and that's
那是一个纯粹的策略，那就是
different from this pure strategy here
与这里的纯策略不同
and so the number of such pure
如此纯净的数量
strategies is 8 so now let's try to make
策略是8，所以现在让我们尝试
that a bit more general generally
一般而言
speaking a pure strategy for
说一个纯粹的策略
player in a perfect information game
完美信息游戏中的玩家
completely specifies how that player
完全指定该玩家的方式
would play the game for anything that
会为任何东西玩游戏
could happen in the game specifically it
可能会在游戏中发生
says what actions to take at every
说出要采取什么行动
choice note that that player gets to
该玩家进入的选择说明
make a decision not so intuitively the
做出不那么直观的决定
way I like to think about pure
我喜欢思考纯净的方式
strategies in an extensive form game is
广泛形式游戏中的策略是
in terms of giving instructions to
在指示
another person to play the game for you
另一个人为您玩游戏
imagine that player 2 wants to send her
想象玩家2想送她
friend off to play the game then she
朋友出去玩游戏，然后她
would need to tell everything to her
需要告诉她一切
friend that her friend might ever need
她的朋友可能需要的朋友
to know in order to play the game
知道为了玩游戏
properly and specifically she'd have to
正确地，特别是她必须
say for every choice node that her
对她的每个选择节点说
friend might encounter what her friend
朋友可能会遇到她的朋友
would need to do so kind of think of a
需要做这样的思考
pure strategy as proxy instructions that
纯策略作为代理指令，
you give to someone else to play the
你给别人玩
game for you then when we're counting
当你数数的时候给你的游戏
the number of pure strategies we really
我们真正的纯粹策略的数量
are asking how many different sets of
在问有多少套不同的
proxy instructions is it possible to
代理说明是否有可能
have if we say this formally in math on
如果我们在数学上正式说这个
the pure strategies of a player in a
一个球员的纯粹策略
given perfect information extensive form
给出完美的信息广泛形式
game are the cross-product of the action
游戏是行动的交叉产物
sets for that play so if we look at the
为这出戏设定，所以如果我们看一下
sets of actions that are available at
在以下位置可用的一组操作
every choice node for the player the set
玩家集合的每个选择节点
of pure strategies is then the
那么纯策略是
cross-product of those sets across all
这些集合在所有方面的叉积
of the choice nodes at which that player
该玩家所在的选择节点
gets to make a decision let's do an
做出决定，让我们做一个
example that is a little bit more
这个例子多一点
complicated than we saw in the sharingan
比我们在共享中看到的复杂
so first of all I want to ask you here
所以首先我想在这里问你
to think what are the pure strategies
思考什么是纯粹的策略
for player 2 here I'm not asking you to
对于这里的玩家2，我不是要你
count them but I'm asking you actually
算他们，但我实际上是在问你
to say what they are and again you may
再说一遍他们是什么
like to pause the video and think about
喜欢暂停视频并考虑
this for both players before I give you
在我给你之前，这两个球员
the answer so we'll start with player -
答案，所以我们将从播放器开始-
well player 2 has two choice nodes this
玩家2有两个选择节点
one here and this one here and so the
这里一个，这里一个，如此
pure strategies for player two are going
第二个人的纯策略正在发展
to be the cross products of the action
成为动作的交叉产物
sets at each of those different choice
着眼于每个不同的选择
nodes so here they are written out so
节点，所以在这里它们被写成
for example the pure strategy CF is
例如，纯策略CF是
saying that if this choice node player
说如果这个选择节点播放器
two will play C and if this choice node
两个将播放C，如果选择节点
player two will play out
玩家二将出局
and because there two sets of size two
而且因为有两套尺寸两个
there's a total of four peer strategies
一共有四种对等策略
now for player one things are a little
现在对于玩家来说，一件事情有点
bit more interesting what are the pure
更有趣的是什么是纯净的
strategies for player one
玩家一的策略
well again player one has two choice
再说一次，玩家一有两个选择
nodes this one and this one and so again
节点这个一个和这个一个等等
the pure strategies for player one are
玩家一的纯粹策略是
the cross product of those two sets so
这两个集合的叉积
again there are four pure strategies for
再次有四个纯策略
player one why is this interesting
玩家一为什么这个很有趣
well if player one takes this action
如果玩家一采取这个行动就好了
then player 1 knows that he will never
然后玩家1知道他永远不会
reach this choice node because his own
到达这个选择节点，因为他自己
action has made it impossible to reach
行动使无法达成
that choice node nevertheless our
那个选择节点仍然是我们
definition of pure strategies says that
纯粹策略的定义说
the pure strategy a G is different from
G的纯策略不同于
the pure strategy aah so there are still
纯粹的策略啊，所以还有
four pure strategies for player one
玩家一的四个纯策略
rather than three pair strategies so
而不是三对策略
pure strategies are a bit different in
纯粹的策略在以下方面有所不同
extensive form games than they were in
比以前广泛的形式游戏
normal form games however there's
普通形式的游戏，但是有
something great once we've got this new
一旦有了新的东西就很棒
definition of pure strategies we can
我们可以定义纯策略
actually leverage it in order to use all
实际利用它来使用所有
of our old definitions of all kinds of
我们对各种
other concepts so in normal forme games
其他的概念，在普通游戏中
we defined mixed strategies as
我们将混合策略定义为
probability distributions over pure
纯概率分布
strategies and in an extensive form game
策略和广泛形式的游戏
we can use exactly the same definition
我们可以使用完全相同的定义
word for word a mixed strategy in an
逐字逐句地混合策略
extensive form game is a probability
广泛的形式游戏是一种可能性
distribution over mixed strategies all
所有混合策略的分布
the changes is that the underlying pure
变化之处在于潜在的纯粹
strategies themselves are different
策略本身是不同的
there now policies of what to do at
现在有在做什么的政策
every choice node in the game likewise a
游戏中的每个选择节点都同样
best response in an extensive form game
在广泛形式的游戏中获得最佳响应
is a mixed strategy that maximizes
是一种最大化的混合策略
expected utility given a mixed strategy
混合策略的预期效用
profile of the other agents so again
其他代理商的个人资料
that's exactly the same definition we
这是我们完全相同的定义
had in the normal form
以正常形式
finally Nash equilibrium is again a
最后纳什均衡又是一个
strategy profile in which every agent is
每个代理都在其中的策略配置文件
best responding to every other agent so
最好对其他每个代理做出回应
all three of these concepts are really
所有这三个概念都是
just the same as they were before now
和以前一样
something we might wonder is
我们可能想知道的是
whether Nash equilibria exist how we can
纳什均衡是否存在，我们如何
reason about them just having the
他们只是拥有的原因
definition doesn't of course give us
定义当然不会给我们
that but there's an even tighter
那，但是有一个更紧密的
connection to the normal form that gives
与正常形式的联系
us more and that is that we can convert
我们更多，那就是我们可以转换
an extensive form game into the normal
普通游戏
form and there are a couple of reasons
形式，有两个原因
why this is interesting the first is
为什么这很有趣首先
because there exists a normal form game
因为存在正常的形式游戏
we can leverage results we have about
我们可以利用我们拥有的结果
the normal form like the existence of
正常形式，如...的存在
equilibrium just by virtue of the fact
仅凭事实就达到均衡
that there's a corresponding game also
还有一个对应的游戏
if we find it easier to reason about the
如果我们发现更容易推理
normal form game we can actually
正常形式的游戏，我们实际上可以
construct it and look at it rather than
构造它，而不是看它
looking at the extensive form so I'm
看着广泛的形式，所以我
going to show you how to do that
将向您展示如何做到这一点
conversion here's the extensive form
转换这里是广泛的形式
game we just thought about the
我们刚刚想到的游戏
conversion is actually really
转换实际上是
straightforward here's the corresponding
简单明了，这是对应的
normal form game and what you'll see is
普通形式的游戏，您会看到的是
we've just listed all of the pure
我们刚刚列出了所有纯
strategies of each agent as the actions
每个行动者的策略作为行动
in the normal form game so you'll
在正常形式的游戏中，这样您就可以
remember these because we went through
记住这些，因为我们经历了
them before in this game already here
他们之前在这个游戏中已经在这里
are the four pure strategies for player
是玩家的四个纯策略
1 and here are the 4 pure strategies for
1和以下是4种纯策略
player 2 now to fill in the payoff
玩家2现在填写收益
values what we do is we just kind of
重视我们所做的就是我们只是
simulate play of the game so if for
模拟游戏的玩法，因此
example I wanted to figure out how to
我想弄清楚如何
put the numbers in this cell of the game
将数字放在游戏的此单元格中
I would look at the pure strategy b:g by
我会看纯策略b：g
player 1 and the pure strategy CF by
玩家1和纯策略CF
player 2
玩家2
so BG means playing like this and CF
所以BG意味着像这样和CF
means playing like that and then I look
就是这样玩，然后我看
at what note I would actually reach in
我实际上会以什么音符到达
the game and I would get down here I'd
游戏，我会在这里下车
follow the tree like that and so I write
跟随那棵树，所以我写
in the number 210 and so this whole
在数字210等整个
table has been filled in that way and
桌子已经被填满了，
this is what we call the induced normal
这就是我们所说的诱发法线
form of this extensive form game now one
这种广泛的形式游戏的形式现在
thing to notice about this induced
关于这一点要注意的事情
normal form is that it has more numbers
正常的形式是它有更多的数字
in it then there are leaf nodes in the
在其中，然后有叶节点
extensive form you'll notice there are
广泛的形式，您会注意到
repetition so for example 3 8 gets
重复，例如3 8得到
repeated four times here even though it
即使在这里重复四次
only corresponds to one payoff
仅对应一次收益
value similarly 8-3 gets repeated four
值类似8-3重复四
times even though it only corresponds to
时间，即使它仅对应于
one payoff value and that's not an
一个回报值，而不是
accident that's because there are four
意外是因为有四个
pure strategy profiles that lead to that
纯粹的战略概况导致
same leaf node in the tree so this can
树中的相同叶节点，因此可以
be a problem because this blow-up is
成为一个问题，因为这种爆炸是
actually exponential it doesn't look so
实际上是指数的，看起来并不像
bad here because the game we're looking
这里不好，因为我们正在寻找的游戏
at is very small but as the size of the
在很小，但随着
game tree grows this blow-up can be
游戏树长大可以炸毁
really profound it can mean that in
真的很深刻，这意味着
practice it might be very difficult for
练习可能很难
us to write down this induce normal form
我们写下这个归纳法则形式
another thing that's important to notice
需要注意的另一件事
is that we can't always do a
是我们不能总是做一个
transformation in Reverse
反向转换
so you might be curious and wonder if
所以你可能很好奇，想知道是否
you give me a normal form game can I
你给我一个普通形式的游戏，我可以吗
make a perfect information extensive
完善信息
form game out of it and the answer is in
形成游戏，答案就在其中
general no this kind of special
一般没有这种特殊
structure that you see to the game where
您在游戏中看到的结构
payoffs are repeated is kind of
回报是重复的
important and general extensive form
重要和一般的广泛形式
games sort of general normal form games
游戏一般的普通形式游戏
can't be turned into extensive form
不能变成广泛的形式
games and an example of that is matching
游戏和一个例子是匹配
pennies intuitively and matching pennies
便士和匹配的便士
it's really important that the two
这两个非常重要
players play simultaneously and we don't
玩家同时玩，我们不
really have a way of talking about two
真的有一种谈论两个的方式
players playing simultaneously in a
玩家在同一时间玩
perfect information game because one of
完美的信息游戏，因为其中之一
the players would have to move first the
玩家必须先移动
second player would then get to see that
然后第二个玩家会看到
move and there's just no way of
移动，没有办法
representing a simultaneous move game
代表同时移动游戏
like matching pennies that way so
像这样匹配便士
intuitively we shouldn't expect a
从直觉上讲，我们不应该期望
transformation from matching pennies
从匹配的便士转变
into a perfect information game seems
成为一个完美的信息游戏
like something would have to be lost
就像必须丢掉一些东西
there indeed there's a theorem that says
确实有一个定理说
that every perfect information extensive
每一个完美的信息都广泛
form game always has at least one pure
形式游戏总是至少有一个纯
strategy Nash equilibrium that's not
策略纳什均衡不是
something that's true in general of
总的来说，这是对的
normal form games matching pennies which
与便士匹配的普通形式的游戏
we just talked about doesn't have a pure
我们刚才说的没有纯粹的
strategy equilibrium it's easy to see
策略均衡很容易看出
why this theorem is true intuitively
为什么这个定理在直觉上是正确的
randomization often serves the role of
随机化通常起着
confusing the other player and there's
混淆了其他玩家，
really no reason that could ever work in
真的没有理由可以在
a perfect information game if player one
一个完美的信息游戏，如果一个人
randomized about this choice and player
随机选择此选项和播放器
two would nevertheless get to see what
两个人仍然会看到
player one had done and so
玩家一已经完成，所以
it can't gain us anything to have
它不能给我们任何东西
randomization in the game that can
游戏中的随机化可以
create the opportunity for an
创造机会
equilibrium that wasn't there before so
以前没有的平衡
lastly I want to look at this game and
最后，我想看看这个游戏，
reason about what it's three pure
三个纯粹的原因
strategy equilibria are now we can do
现在我们可以做到策略均衡
this by actually looking at the game
通过实际看比赛
tree and trying to think about what
树，试图思考什么
would make sense as an equilibrium in
作为在
that game but that can be a little bit
那个游戏，但是可能有点
hard to do in part because we can't
很难做的部分原因是我们不能
quite so easily read the pure strategies
非常容易地阅读纯策略
off the game tree instead what can be
从游戏树上掉下来
more convenient for a small game like
像这样的小游戏更方便
this is to construct it's pure strategy
这是构建它的纯策略
its induced normal form here which lists
它的诱导范式在这里列出
the pure strategies directly and then to
直接的纯策略然后
just reason about the pure strategies
纯粹策略的正当理由
directly on this game so let's do that
直接在这个游戏上，所以让我们做到这一点
so I'll let you again pause the video
所以我会让你再次暂停视频
here if you like and try to find those
在这里，如果您喜欢并尝试找到那些
equilibria for yourself and then I'll
为自己平衡，然后我会
tell you what they are so the three
告诉你他们是什么，那三个
Peter strategy equilibria are a GCF a
彼得策略均衡是GCF
HCF and bhc so let's talk about how
HCF和bhc，让我们谈谈如何
we're able to see that those are
我们能够看到那些是
equilibria recall always the way that we
均衡总是回想着我们
test for a pure strategy equilibrium in
测试一个纯粹的战略均衡
a normal form game is to for each player
一个普通的形式游戏是给每个玩家
check and see whether there's any
检查一下是否有
deviation that would give that player
会给那个球员的偏差
greater utility so let's for example
更大的实用性，让我们举个例子
look at bhce if player one was to
看bhce，如果玩家一
deviate here you can see there's no
偏离这里，你可以看到那里没有
other action he could take that would
他可以采取的其他措施
give him more than five and similarly if
给他五个以上，如果
player 2 was to deviate here you can see
玩家2偏离这里可以看到
there's no other action she could take
她别无选择
that would give her more than 5 in both
两者都给她超过5
cases there's something that would tie
情况下，有些东西会绑在一起
but that's ok because a best response
但这没关系，因为最好的回应
just says that there isn't anything
只是说没有什么
better so that confirms that this is an
更好地确认这是一个
equilibrium in contrast if I looked at
相反，如果我看着
something like this which I've claimed
我声称这样的事情
isn't an equilibrium you can see that it
不是均衡，你可以看到它
isn't an equilibrium by checking for
通过检查不是平衡
each player's so player 2 indeed can't
每个玩家的，所以玩家2确实不能
do anything better than ten so this is a
做任何事情都超过十，所以这是一个
best response as CF is a
最佳响应，因为CF是
response to BG for player two but on the
对玩家2的BG的回应，但在
other hand player one could deviate from
另一只手玩家可能会偏离
BG to AG and get a payoff of three
BG到AG并获得三分收益
instead of a payoff of two so a BG is
而不是两个的回报，所以BG是
not a best response to CF for player one
不是玩家一对CF的最佳回应
and so this is not a Nash equilibrium
所以这不是纳什均衡
and that's it for this video thanks
这就是这个视频，谢谢